Guide to the Cause Marketing Forum. Halo Awards Records, 2002-2012 and undated RL.11128
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 2002-2012 and undated; 12
  - Originals, 2002-2012 and undated; 99
    - Jumpstart Read for the Record Public Service Announcement with LL Cool J, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-010)
    - American Express/Share Our Strength "No Kid Hungry", 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-011)
    - Protecting Futures Highlight Reel, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-012)
    - A Million Reasons to Believe broadcast summary, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-013)
    - I Am the Cure (Komen Race for the Cure), undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-014)
    - L'Oreal Kerry Washington/Ovarian Cancer PSA and Survivor Interview, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-015)
    - L'Oreal Color of Hope Broadcast Press Clips, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-016)
    - Energizer ReTreat supporting materials, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-017)
    - Summer Streets, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-018)
    - Millsports/Sunchips/Susan G. Komen, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-019)
    - Sunchips Halo Award images, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-020)
    - BMRC artwork, 2006 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-021)
    - Pedigree campaign images and logos, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-022)
    - Catapult Dog Adoption Drive, 2006 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-023)
    - Classroomscape Materials, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-024)
    - Jumpstart files, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-025)
    - Make a Wish: We All Have the Power, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-026)
    - American Cancer Society, Pink Ribbon campaign, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-027)
    - A Million Reasons to Believe sizzle reel, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-028)
    - A Million Reasons to Believe print summary, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-029)
    - Subaru Share the Love, 2009 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-030)
    - Rally for the Cure, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-031)
    - Safe Drive Stay Alive US Pilot Program, Monte Vista High School Event Highlights, 2007 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-032)
    - Safe Drive Stay Alive US Pilot Program, Monte California High School Full version, 2007 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-033)
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop, Huggable Heroes, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-034)
    - L'Oreal Lifetime commercials featuring 2006 honorees, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-035)
    - L'Oreal Employees of Worth, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-036)
    - L'Oreal Women of Worth Honoree Profiles, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-037)
    - L'Oreal Women of Worth Honoree Press clips, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-038)
    - Subway/American Heart Association Fresh Fit, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-039)
    - GSN/National Vocabulary Championship Win with Words, 2007 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-040)
    - Cartoon Network Rescuing Recess, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-041)
    - Operation Kids New Orleans clips, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-042)
    - Operation Kids Rebuilding Dreams in New Orleans, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-043)
    - Energizer ReTreat FY2007 Media Recap, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-044)
    - Rally for the Cure, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-045)
    - Pedigree Adoption Drive, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-046)
    - National Marrow Donor Program "Be the Match" :60 TV, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-047)
    - National Marrow Donor Program "Be the Match" radio, out of home, print, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-048)
    - Jumpstart Read for the Record 2009 Event toolkit (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-049)
    - Jumpstart NBC affiliate piece, 2009 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-050)
    - Jumpstart NBC Today Show segment, 13:55, 2009 Oct. 8 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-051)
    - Samsung Hope for Education, 2005 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-052)
    - 2nd Annual Hope for Education, 2005 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-053)
    - Coca-Cola Community All-Americans promotional video, 2004 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-054)
    - Coca-Cola Community All-Americans winners video, 2004-2005 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-055)
    - Ford Cares, This One's for You, :69, 2005 September 6 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-056)
    - Komen Race for the Cure conference video, 2006 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-057)
    - Nothing but Nets Mali photos, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-058)
    - Nothing but Nets video (requires Quicktime and RealPlayer, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-059)
    - American Red Cross/Curel, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-060)
    - Ferrero Rocher/Share Our Strength, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-061)
    - A Million Reasons to Believe broadcast summary, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-062)
    - Macy's "Yes, Virginia" V2, :30, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-063)
    - CBS Early Show, Macy's Believe Campaign for Make a Wish, 16:50, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-064)
    - AT&T Team USA Soundtrack, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-065)
    - Autism Speaks, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-066)
    - Coca-Cola/USO, untitled, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-067)
    - United Airlines, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-068)
    - Midas, Change a Life, 2:15, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-069)
    - Toys R Us Guide for Differently-Abled Kids, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-070)
    - Keep Gym in School, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-071)
    - Toys for Tots Literacy Program video clips, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-072)
    - Women of Worth Style, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-073)
    - Women of Worth TNT, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-074)
    - Women of Worth Lifetime, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-075)
    - Women of Worth WETV, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-076)
    - Women of Worth TVLand, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-077)
    - Women of Worth 2008 Honoree Profiles (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-078)
    - Women of Worth broadcast press clips, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11030-DVD-079)
    - Cotton. From Blue to Green video, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-080)
    - Cotton. From Blue to Green photos, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-081)
    - Cotton Incorporated: Focus on Sustainability, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-082)
    - TripAdvisor YouTube video, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-083)
    - Salvation Army CD spot "Holiday Cause, Channel Red", 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-084)
    - Trees for Troops photos, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-085)
    - ASAE Summit Award Trees for Troops, 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-086)
    - Rock the Vote Mobile Powered by AT&T, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-087)
    - Warriors in Pink 2008 Recap with metrics (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-088)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 1, NLV0100613, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-089)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 1, NLV0100614, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-090)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 1, NLV01006115, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-091)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 1, NLV0100616, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-092)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 1, NLV0100617, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-093)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 2, NLV0102171, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-094)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 2, NLV0102173, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-095)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 2, NLV0102174, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-096)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 2, NLV0102175, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-097)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 4, NLV0100824, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-098)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 4, NLV0100825, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-099)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 4, NLV0100826, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-100)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 4, NLV0100827, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-101)
    - HGTV: Change the World. Start at Home PSAs Group 4, NLV0100828, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-102)
    - Toys for Tots, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-103)
    - Toys for Tots Literacy Program video clips, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-104)
    - Macy's/Reading is Fundamental, Book a Brighter Future promotional video, Miami Book Fair, 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-105)
    - Aramark Building Community broadcast media coverage samples, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-106)
    - Warriors in Pink 2008 Recap with metrics (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-107)
    - Gibson Music Rising EPK, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-108)
    - YAI Halo Awards, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-109)
    - Blockbuster/Boys and Girls Clubs of America promotion, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-110)
    - Go Organic! Entry materials, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-111)
    - Aldo Broll, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-112)
    - Energizer Change Your Clock Change Your Battery program results and media highlights, 2005 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-113)
    - Esurance Save Our Selves, 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-114)
    - Chase the Extraordinary tour video, 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-115)
    - Live Earth Sizzle Reel 2:00, 2007 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-116)
    - Live Earth Film Series: Sad Fish, Devils Rulebook, Mermaid, Don't Let It All Unravel, 2007 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-117)
    - Live Earth "Control Room" Celebrity PSA Submission 25:35, 2007 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-118)
    - Playskool & Boundless Playgrounds "Let's All Play...It Matters!" supporting materials, 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-119)
    - Skin Cancer Takes Friends highlights, 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-120)
    - Olay/ASDS Skin Cancer Screenings participation kit, 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-121)
    - American Diabetes Association "I Decide to Fight Diabetes" campaign 3:25, 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-122)
    - Liberty Medical spots: ZMAI7663 "Empowerment" :60; ZMAI7660 "Costs" :60; ZMAI7694 "Caregiver" :60; ZMAI7666 "Choices: :60, 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-123)
    - Chili's Create a Pepper media overview 3:46, 2007 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-124)
    - Chili's Create a Pepper radio psa 1:30, 2007 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-125)
    - Chili's Create a Pepper employee video 10:22, 2007 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-126)
    - Chili's Create a Pepper radio psa DJ endorsements, 2007 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-127)
    - DonorsChoose media: Oprah Winfrey "Great Teachers" 7:00; Today Show "DonorsChoose Breaks $1 million" 7:00; DonorsChoose documentary 8:00; PSAs 2:00; ABC Nightline "DonorsChoose: One Good Idea" 21:00, 2008 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-128)
    - Eco Bunnies, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-129)
    - Sunkist Take a Stand PSAs :45, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-130)
    - Sunkist Take a Stand highlights 2006 Oct. 16, 2:30 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-131)
    - Sunkist Take a Stand Billy Dean Fox and Friends Saturday, 4:42, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-132)
    - Sunkist Take a Stand, Talk of the Town WTVF, 5:44, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-133)
    - Sunkist Take a Stand, Good Things Utah KTVX, 12:26, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-134)
    - Rimington Trophy media coverage, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-135)
    - McDonald's "24 Hour Bar Promo", 2007 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-136)
    - Fox News, Fox and Friends, Morning News, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-137)
    - Ambassadors of Rock, Hard Rock Café New York, Motley Crue Highlights, undated (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-138)
    - Hard Rock International's Ambassadors of Rock in New York, 2007 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-139)
    - Dr. Phil, Toys for Tots, EPK/PSAs 11-15-06, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-140)
    - Dr. Phil, Christmas Show, OAD 12-11-06, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-141)
    - Dr. Phil, Spoiled and Entitled, OAD 11-30-06, 2006 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-142)
    - Bing Our School Needs videos: Call to Action; How to Make; Josh Grobin School Visit; Finalists Montage; OSN Wrap-Up Video, 2010 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-143)
    - Bing Our School Needs broadcast clips, 2-3-11, 2011 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-144)
    - Bing Jimmy Fallon, 2010 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-145)
    - Liberty Mutual National Conversation Drive supporting materials, 2011 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-146)
    - Sesame Street Food for Thought (English and Spanish), 2010 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11030-DVD-147)
    - Sesame Street On-air sponsorship 1:30, 2010 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-148)
    - Toys R Us, Autism Speaks, 2011 (Box AV3, Dvd RL11030-DVD-149)
    - Unicef, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-150)
    - National Lung Cancer Partnership, Free to Breathe TV PSA :30, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-151)
    - RADD, BTS, PSA, PR party, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-152)
    - CARE Join My Village 4x3, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-153)
    - Africa Initiatives: Join My Village GMI; Join My Village non-GMI; Malawi--Phil, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-154)
    - Cycle for Survival, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-155)
    - History Channel, Vietnam in HD "Call for Photos" campaign video recap, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-156)
    - Day at UN Clean & Clear Hero, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-157)
    - Stream Energy Halo Award submission video footage, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-158)
    - No Kid Hungry audio news release, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-159)
    - Makeovers for Military's Night Out disc, untitled, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-160)
    - TRU Autism Campaign video final, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-161)
    - Redskins Touchdown for Tots, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-162)
    - Local broadcast coverage of Kohl's donation to the Milwaukee Art Museum, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-163)
    - Kohl's Kids Who Care radio and television clips :45, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-164)
    - No Kid Hungry highlight reel and PSAs, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-165)
    - Time Warner Cable's Connect a Million Minds, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-166)
    - Viacommunity Annual Report 2008-2009, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-167)
    - Step and Close, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-168)
    - Catapult Marketing/Reckitt Benckiser/Dollar General Halo Awards, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-169)
    - Ben & Jerry Hubby Hubby Halo Award Entry, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-170)
    - History Channel, Take a Veteran to School Day, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-171)
    - Rally for the Cure Ambassador Thank You, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-172)
    - Sonic Limeades for Learning TV, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-173)
    - Ford Warriors in Pink recap video, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-174)
    - Stop Bullying Speak Up pro-social campaign, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-175)
    - Stop Bullying Speak Up, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-176)
    - Benjamin Moore Color Care Across America sample event video, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-177)
    - Walk with Walgreens supporting video, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-178)
    - Walk with Walgreens supporting video, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-179)
    - VSP Eye Pledge, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-180)
    - Zynga/Save the Children videos, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-181)
    - Pepto-Bismol Throws a Feast for All, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-182)
    - Unicef Champions for Children recruitment video, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-183)
    - Unicef Change for Good Program on American Airlines in-flight video 3:23, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-184)
    - Bank of America Gift for Opportunity Fund video assets, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-185)
    - Outback Steakhouse Thanks for Giving, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-186)
    - Procter & Gamble Road to Reunion, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-187)
    - State Farm Go to Bat promotion, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-188)
    - Multiple Schlerosis Brain Game, 2008 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-189)
    - The Recovery Project, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-190)
    - Voices Remember, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-191)
    - T-Mobile Huddle Up for New Orleans, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-192)
    - Uncle Ben's Fuels Feeding America's Kids Café Program, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-193)
    - Good Morning America, Warm Coats and Warm Hearts Drive disc 1, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-194)
    - Good Morning America, Warm Coats and Warm Hearts Drive disc 2, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-195)
    - Share Our Hope, Share Our Strength; videos and clips, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-196)
    - Campbell Soup/Fufure Farmers of America, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-197)
    - Jones New York in the Classroom, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-198)
    - Be Big! Ten Days, Ten Ways promo, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-199)
    - Avon Hello Green Tomorrow powerpoint, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-200)
    - Child Hunger Ends Here campaign overview, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-201)
    - Save the Children Celebrity video, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-202)
    - Save the Children video, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-203)
    - Time Warner Cable's Connect a Million Minds, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-204)
    - P&G Walmart spot, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-205)
    - Arm Yourself with a Walgreens Flu Shot supporting video, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-206)
    - Child Hunger Ends Here campaign overview, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-207)
    - Great Wolf Resorts, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-208)
    - OfficeMax A Day Made Better pledges, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-209)
    - Dallas Moustache, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-210)
    - Cheesecake Factory, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-211)
    - USO/Old Navy Diva, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-212)
    - USO/Old Navy Diva in-show moment, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-213)
    - No Kid Hungry PSA, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-214)
    - Disney images, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-215)
    - Home Safety Council, Code Red Rover Grownup Come Over, 2006 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-216)
    - History Channel Save Our History program overview, 2006 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-217)
    - History Channel Heritage Tourism Partnership, 2006 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-218)
    - History Channel Heritage Tourism Partnership, 2006 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-219)
    - ITT Watermark videos, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-220)
    - Georgia Pacific Wellness Mantra TV, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-221)
    - New Balance Pink Ribbon Workouts, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-222)
    - Toys R Us, Toys for Tots video footage, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-223)
    - Pink Together video for screen displays, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-224)
    - Pink video, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-225)
    - Pink for the Cure Biggest Loser, song, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-226)
    - Pink Together theme song and video, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-227)
    - Toys R Us Great Trade-In interviews, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-228)
    - Toys R Us Great Trade-In, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-229)
    - Biggest Loser Pound for Pound Challenge episodes 701-711 short versions, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-230)
    - Biggest Loser Pound for Pound Challenge episodes 712-718 short versions, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-231)
    - Biggest Loser Pound for Pound Challenge episodes 719-719a, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-232)
    - Biggest Loser Pound for Pound Challenge episode 709, General Mills Food Bank Challenge, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-233)
    - American Kidney Fund Pair Up, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-234)
    - Disney Friends for Change games, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-235)
    - Pringles USA Taste of Home, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-236)
    - American Cancer Society, Choose You documentary, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-237)
    - Pirates of the Caribbean Boys and Girls Club premiere, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-238)
    - USO Military Bowl Charlie Mann commercial, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-239)
    - Bounty's We Love Our School campaign, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-240)
    - Great Wolf Resorts, 2012 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-241)
    - Tostitos Fiesta in the Square, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-242)
    - The French Will Never Forget 9/11 Tribute, 2011 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-243)
    - Stop Diabetes, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-244)
    - Hasbro Project Zambi, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-245)
    - Salvation Army Intervention Town Hall, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-246)
    - H&R Block Dollars and Sense media tour clips, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-247)
    - H&R Block Dollars and Sense web content, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-248)
    - H&R Block Dollars and Sense convention video loop, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-249)
    - H&R Block Dollars and Sense web content, 2009 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-250)
    - Take a Veteran to School Day, 2010 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-251)
    - Verizon Extra Credit for Schools: Tell Us What Your School Needs Most, 2004 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-252)
    - Parade/Share Our Strength Great American Bake Sale, 2004 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-253)
    - Bowl for the Cure, 2003 (Box AV4, Dvd RL11030-DVD-254)
    - Nothing But Nets spots, 2007 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-255)
    - Personal Reflections: Patient Stories of Brain Tumors TRT 45:00, 2006 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-256)
    - Darfur screensaver, 2007 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-257)
    - Volvo for Life Awards photos, 2007 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-258)
    - Volvo for Life Awards Documentaries and PSAs, 2007 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-259)
    - Volvo for Life Awards Media highlights, 2007 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-260)
    - HSBC Your Money Counts, 2006 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-261)
    - HSBC Your Money Counts Training Materials, 2006 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-262)
    - Clifford Be Big Campaign, 2009 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-263)
    - Clifford the Big Red Dog 10 Big Ideas TRT 10:00, 2009 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-264)
    - CYBEX Pink Ribbon Run marketing materials, 2009 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-265)
    - Toys R Us Toy Guide for Differently Abled Kids digital files, 2009 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-266)
    - Heroes at Home :60 spot Letter Home, 2009 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-267)
    - Heroes at Home PA announcement, 2009 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-268)
    - NECCO Today footage, 2009 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-269)
    - Kohl's 2010 giveback campaign national TV spot :30 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-270)
    - PUR and the Summit on the Summit Program, 2011 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-271)
    - World Vision's End Malaria Campaign, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-272)
    - Kohl's Cares Cause Merchandise Program to Support Women's Health, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-273)
    - NDSS My Great Story clips and footage, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-274)
    - TELUS Go Pink, 2011 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-275)
    - All Pro Dad. Chunky Promo Tony Dungy and Bettis Fox and Friends; Dungy on Mad Dog Radio, 2011 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-276)
    - Kroger Giving Hope a Hand Breast Cancer Montage, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-277)
    - Be a Good Cookie short video clips, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-278)
    - Be a Good Cookie results video, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-279)
    - Southwest Airlines Tour 40, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-280)
    - JetBlue Soar with Reading Photos 1, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-281)
    - JetBlue Soar with Reading Photos 2, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-282)
    - JetBlue Soar with Reading Recap video, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-283)
    - JetBlue Soar with Reading PSA :30, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-284)
    - Build-a-Bear Workshop, Huggable Heroes, compilation video, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-285)
    - Duracell Power Those Who Protect Us campaign, 2012 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-286)
    - TELUS Go Pink, 2011 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-287)
    - Walmart and Procter & Gamble Operation Family Connect, 2010 (Box AV6, Dvd RL11030-DVD-288)